Open a window and click on the triangle on the right side of the window name to change the window in the salad menu
Then select Hot Key List
At the top of each main section, the basic common shortcut keys will be folded
Click on the triangle on the left side of the secondary title to display the shortcut keys that can be used when the window function is active
Click on the gray arrow on the right side of the main section name to fold the entire section of the shortcut keys to display
Click on the white arrow on the top of each main section to display the shortcut key
When you open and display the shortcut key window, select a tool and the relevant shortcut keys will automatically appear in the center of the shortcut key window
To change the shortcut key function, click on the semantics of the shortcut key
After selecting the shortcut key function on the left, click on the red arrow on the right side of the screen to change the shortcut key function
Thank you for watching and see you in the next video.